Finding aid for the Karl G. Yoneda papers, 1892-1998, bulk 1925-1989 LSC.1592
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 6. Investigation Case Files, 1941-1980
  - Department of the Air Force, 1960 September 30 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Photocopies of documents held by the Department of the Air Force. Also includes a letter from the Department of the Air Force. Reference number: 100-19133-62 (September 30, 1960).
- 7. Japanese American Citizens League, 1950-1989
  Series comprised of materials regarding the Japanese American Citizens League. Includes newsletters, leaflets, pamphlets, letters, notes, and news clippings.
  - 7.1 Bay Area Community Chapter and Golden Gate Chapter, 1970-1989
    Contains newsletters, leaflets, letters, notes, and news clippings of the Bay Area Community Chapter and the Golden Gate Chapter of the Japanese American Citizens League (JACL) from 1970 to 1989.
    - Bay Area Community Chapter, 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bay Area Community Chapter, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Bay Area Community Chapter, 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Bay Area Community Chapter, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Bay Area Community Chapter, 1976-1977 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Golden Gate Chapter, 1984-1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 7.2 Events and Related Materials, 1950-1989
    Contains materials regarding events supported by the JACL, including the campaign for the repeal of Title II of the Emergency Detention Act and the campaign for the Tokyo Rose case. There is also a file containing materials on Mike Masaoka, who was the national executive secretary of the JACL. The materials mainly include letters, leaflets, pamphlets, notes, and news clippings.
    - Campaign for the Repeal of Title II of the Emergency Detention Act, 1968-1972 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Campaign for the Tokyo Rose Case, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Mike Masaoka, 1963-1988 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Materials Regarding the JACL, 1950-1989 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- 8. Correspondence, 1925-1996
  Series contains mainly incoming correspondence from individuals, organizations, and institutions. Also includes Yoneda's letters.
  - 8.1 Family Correspondence, 1941, 1950-1993
    Incoming correspondence from Yoneda's family members.
    - Kazu Yoneda, 1941 February 22, 1950 December 27-1976 August 3 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      Mostly photocopies of correspondence from Kazu Yoneda. In Japanese.
    - Other Relatives, 1954-1993 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Incoming correspondence from Kubo family, siblings, son, grandchildren, and other relatives.
  - 8.2 Japanese American Oral History Program, 1973-1975
    Letters from members of the Japanese American Oral History Program, California State University, Fullerton.
    - Japanese American Oral History Program, 1973-1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      Incoming correspondence from Arthur A. Hansen, Ronald C. Larson, and Susan McNamara, and Betty E. Mitson. Some letters address Elaine Yoneda. Also includes abridged translation from "History of 100 Years of Japanese Immigrants in America" by Shinkichi Kato, excerpts from interview of Herbert V. Nicholson, and a news clipping.
  - 8.3 Japanese Publishers, 1975-1993
    Correspondence with Japanese publishers, including ??? Kodansha, ?????? Nihon Hoso Kyokai, PMC?? PMC Shuppan, ?????? Shin Nihon Shuppansha, and ????? Toho Shuppansha.
    - ??? Kodansha, 1977, 1983, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      Correspondence regarding "Encyclopedia of Japan", to which Yoneda contributed by submitting his articles. Also includes drafts of Yoneda's articles and letters, and a news clipping.
    - ?????? Nihon Hoso Kyokai, 1989 September 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      One letter from Yoshiki Inomata.
    - PMC?? PMC Shuppan, 1987-1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      Incoming correspondence from Kazuhisa Imai and copies of Yoneda's letters, receipts for loyalty payments, and the agreement documents signed by Yoneda and the PMC.
    - ?????? Shin Nihon Shuppansha, 1978-1989 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Incoming correspondence from Kunio Takano, Takashi Tsuda, and Shiro Tanaka, copies of Yoneda's letters to Shun Nishizawa, Kunio Takano, and Shiro Tanaka.
    - ????? Toho Shuppansha, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      One letter from Mahito Fujiyama.
  - 8.4 Ordering Letters for Yoneda's Publication, 1967-1969
    Incoming correspondence from individuals and institutions requesting copies of Yoneda's book, "History of Japanese Labor in the United States," and a list of the requesters compiled by Yoneda. Receipts from the publisher and news clippings on the book are also included.
    - Ordering Letters for Yoneda's Publication, 1967-1969 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - 8.5 Incoming Correspondence, 1925-1946, 1951-1996
    Correspondence from individuals, including communist members, labor union members, other activists, scholars, individual researchers, organizations, and institutions. There are two folders containing early correspondence including incoming letters and postcards from Japanese activists, which were mailed to Yoneda in Hiroshima between 1925 and 1926, prior to his returning to the United States in 1927. Also Includes copies and drafts of Yoneda's letters.
    - Early Correspondence (1 of 2), circa 1925-1926 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Includes incoming correspondence to Yoneda from ??? Tan Etsuta, T. Kubo, ??? Izumi Shigeo, and ???? Maeda Kinuko, and also includes two postcards mailed to Yoneda from ??? Nakahama Tetsu, who was imprisoned in an Osaka prison, and a photograph of ??? Nakahama Tetsu, the Guillotine league, Osaka, Japan, in 1925. All in Japanese.
    - Early Correspondence (2 of 2), circa 1925-1926, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Includes one letter from ???? Tanno Setsu mailed to ???? Watanabe Tetsu written on January 30, 1929, with a stamp of ?????????? Kaiho Undo Giseisha Kyuenkai, and letters addressing ??? Kawato Minoru. Also includes letters mailed from China. All written in Japanese.
    - Individuals: A, 1952-1954, 1966-1969, 1976-1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      Includes Akita, Karl; Ariyoshi, Koji.
    - Individuals: B, 1968, 1977-1980 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Archie, 1942 April-1943 October (Box 34, Folder 14)
      Correspondence from Yoneda to Archie Brown, including postcards and letters mailed from the Owens Valley Reception Center, Manzanar, California; F.S.A. Camp Filer Idaho; Camp Shelby, Miss.; and Camp Savage, Minn. There is one photograph of Yoneda with other crews at sugar beets fields, Filer, Idaho, taken on October 11, 1942.
    - Individuals: C-E, 1972-1984 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Individuals: F, 1956, 1964, 1971-1985, 1993, and undated (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Forsyth, Ian, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 17)
      Correspondence from Ian Forsyth. Also includes photocopies of Forsyth's academic records, English translation of the preface in Yoneda's publication, and other documents.
    - ???? Fukuda, Keiko, 1961-1965, 1982-1989, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      Correspondence from ???? Fukuda, Keiko (= ???? Akiba, Keiko) who is an artist and author of "????? Biruma no Hana = Flower of Burma." Includes documents regarding the NHK TV program based on her book, Yoneda's newspaper articles, news clippings, pamphlets, photographs, and postcards of paintings by Keiko Fukuda and his father.
    - Individuals: G-H, 1958, 1968-1983, and undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Individuals: I, 1977-1985, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      Includes Yoneda's letters to Prof. Yuji Ichioka.
    - ???? Ito, Kazuo, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      Correspondence from ???? Ito Kazuo and copies of Yoneda's letter. Includes newspaper articles by Kazuo Ito, titled: ???????? ??????????? Kashu Dokyumentari Amerika Dendenmushi.
    - Individuals: J-K, 1931, 1953-1993, and undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ???? Kasama, Shozo, 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      Correspondence from Shozo Kasama, the representative of ????????? Jakku Shirai Kenkyukai.
    - ??? Kawanari, Yo, 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      Correspondence from Yo Kawanari, a member of ????????? Jakku Shirai Kenkyukai, including his publications.
    - ??????? Kochi, Poru Shinsei, 1971-1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Individuals: L-M, 1968-1989 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      Folder includes correspondence regarding the interviews of Karl and Elaine Yoneda with Edward Murata, Joyce Sakamoto, and Linda Fujikawa, as well as questions the interviewers intended to ask during the interview. This folder does not include transcripts.
    - ???? Matsuo, Shoichi, 1982-1992 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Individuals: N, 1966-1992 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      Includes Jimmy [Arima] Nakamura.
    - ????? Nishiuji, Tsunejiro, 1963-1988 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      Correspondence from Tsunejiro Nishiuji, a member of Japanese Communist Party.
    - ???? Nosaka, Sanzo, 1965-1989 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      Correspondence from Sanzo Nosaka, the Chairman of the Japanese Communist Party. Also includes Yoneda's letters and his draft of meeting notes when meeting with Sanzo Nosaka.
    - North American Committee for Democratic Japan New York Members, 1946 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      Includes incoming correspondence from the members of the North American Committee for Democratic Japan, New York.
    - Individuals: O, 1963-1978 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - ???? Omae, Senkei and His Family, 1960-1973 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      Letters from ???? Omae Akiko; ???? Omae Senkei; ???? Omae Kikuko; Omae Asaichi. Also includes photographs and pamphlets.
    - Individuals: P-R, 1953-1954, 1969-1988 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Individuals: S, 1940, 1971-1992 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - ??? Seki, Kozo, 1983-1988 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      Correspondence from Kozo Seki, a member of ????????? Jakku Shirai Kenkyukai.
    - ????? Shiota, Shobei, 1964-1993 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      Contains mainly correspondence from Yoneda, including his articles and news clippings. Also includes one letter from ????? Nishiuji Tsunejiro.
    - Individuals: T-W, 1941, 1967, 1976-1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Includes letters from Karl Akihito Tsuji.
    - Weglyn, Michi Nishiura, 1986-1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      Correspondence from Michi Nishiura Weglyn along with photocopies of documents. Includes tribute to her and one issue of "Japanese American National Museum."
    - Individuals: Y, 1946, 1960-1993 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Individuals: Unidentified, 1951-1996 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      Includes letters from unidentified individuals.
    - Organizations: Acknowledgment Letters, 1964-1995 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Acknowledgment letters for donations, subscriptions, etc.
    - Institutions: Talks and Lectures, 1970-1986 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Letters regarding Yoneda's talks and lectures.
- 9. Personal Memorabilia, 1933-1998
  Series contains letters for the Japanese American Research Project/Issei History Project; Yoneda's family photographs; travel journals; news clippings; and other personal materials. There are folders containing materials regarding Kazu Yoneda and Elaine Yoneda.
  - 9.1 Japanese American Research Project/Issei History Project, 1965-1990
    Contains correspondence from Joe Grant Masaoka, the UCLA Japanese American Research Project, Prof. Yuji Ichioka, and Rio Yamane; copies of Yoneda's letters with his handwritten notes on Issei and Nisei socialists, communists, trade unionists, and liberals; and copies of Ben Kobashigawa's proposal for his postdoctoral research project.
    - Japanese American Research Project/Issei History Project, 1965-1990 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - 9.2 Photographs, 1933-1986
    Photographs of Yoneda and his family members.
    - Photographs of Yoneda and His Family Members, 1933-1986 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Photographs of Karl and Elaine Yoneda with their family members and others. English captions are attached to some of the photographs.
    - Karl G. Yoneda, circa 1988 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      A black and white photograph of Yoneda.
  - 9.3 Journals and Tour Materials, 1967-1995
    Contains journals documenting Yoneda's activities between 1967 and 1955.
    - NJAHS Calendars, 1989-1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      National Japanese American Historical Society's calendars of 1989, 1990, 1992, and 1995, recording Yoneda's daily activities. In English.
    - Japan Travel Journals, 1972 and 1979 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      Yoneda's handwritten Japan travel journals in 1972 and 1979. In English and Japanese.
    - Moscow Travel Journal, 1973 October 23-29 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      Handwritten Moscow travel journal from October 23 through 29, 1973. In Japanese.
    - USSR Tour Materials, 1967 October-November (Box 36, Folder 12)
      Includes correspondence from American Russian Institute, International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union, Communist Party of Northern California, and a tour agency, Globe Tours. Includes itineraries In Russian and a brochure in English.
  - 9.4 Personal Information, 1942, 1961-1967, 1984-1988, 1993
    Contains materials for Yoneda's personal events, including wedding anniversary announcements, moving announcements, his loan agreement, receipts, photocopies of his birth certificate, his request for revocation of dual citizenship issued in 1942 with English translation, and a letter from a social worker of the Kimochi Care and Support for Japanese American Elders informing his son of Yoneda's condition.
    - Personal Information, 1961-1967, 1984-1988, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Personal Events, 1947-1983 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - 9.5 News Clippings on Elaine and Karl Yoneda, 1952, 1971-1998
    News clippings, fliers, featuring Elaine and Karl Yoneda. Includes an illustration of Yoneda.
    - News Clippings on Elaine and Karl Yoneda, 1952, 1971-1998 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 9.6 Kazu Yoneda, 1976
    Contains photographs of Yoneda's mother, Kazu Yoneda, and her grave stone in Japan; her obituaries; a telegram from Japan to inform of her death; her biographies compiled by Yoneda; announcement of her memorial services held in Los Angeles with notes for the expenses; and sympathy letters received.
    - Kazu Yoneda, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - 9.7 Elaine Yoneda, 1976
    Documents regarding Elaine Yoneda, including photographs depicting her political activities; a diary written during her incarceration in the Manznar War Relocation Center between March 16 and December 19, 1942; materials documenting her grievances at the ILWU-PMA Benefit Fund Office; documents regarding her archive collection donated to the Labor Archives and Research Center; and other documents, including news clippings, membership cards, correspondence, transcripts of her talks, her obituaries, and her biographical information. There is a folder for the Elaine Yoneda Memorial Book Committee including meeting notes, letters, fliers, and news clippings.
    - Labor Archives and Research Center, 1986-1997 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      Release agreement regarding Elaine Black Yoneda's archive collection donated to the Labor Archives and Research Center, letters, and other documents.
    - Photographs, 1934-1936, 1941 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      Photographs of Elaine Yoneda's political activities, including visiting Tom Mooney and other political prisoners; participating in Herndon's nation tour for "Free the Scottsboro Boys and Angelo Herndon;" attending memorial services of the 1935 Holmes Eureka Lumber strike victims; visiting the Holmes Eureka Lumber Co. with Archie Brown; attending the funeral for Jim B. McNamara, a Los Angeles Times case victim; and leading the ILWU Auxiliaries at the 1937 San Francisco Labor Day march.
    - Elaine Yoneda's Manzanar Diary, 1942 March 16-December 19 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      A diary written by Elaine Yoneda during her incarceration in the Manzanar War Relocation Center, March 16-December 19, 1942. In English.
    - International Longshoremen's & Warehousemen's Union Pacific Maritime Association Benefit Funds, 1957-1972 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      Materials regarding Elaine Yoneda's grievances at the ILWU-PMA Benefit Fund Office.
    - Miscellaneous Documents on Elaine Yoneda, 1934-1993 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      News clippings on Elaine Yoneda's ILWU activities, membership cards, transcripts of her radio speech broadcasted on October 26, 1939 and talk on women in Japan given on September 29, 1972, correspondence to her received in 1930s, obituaries, transcripts of Yoneda's tribute to her, and her biographical information.
    - Elaine Yoneda Memorial Book Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      The committee's meeting notes, letters, fliers, and news clippings.
- 10. Political Subject Files, 1892-1995 bulk 1945-1995
  Series includes folders of activists, Japanese American individuals, and political activities and subjects. Contains Yoneda's notes, photographs, correspondence, and collected publications, including pamphlets, brochures, newsletters, fliers, and news clippings.
  - 10.1 Activists and Japanese American Individuals, 1892-1937, 1945-1995
    Contains Yoneda's notes, photographs, correspondence, pamphlets, news clippings, and obituaries regarding activists and Japanese American individuals. Includes photocopied materials originally published from 1892 to 1937. In English and Japanese. All folders are arranged alphabetically.
    - ?????? Abiko, Kyutaro, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - ????? Baba, Kosaburo, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      Includes materials regarding the Oxnard strike.
    - Brown, Archie, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Bridges, Harry and Noriko, 1972-1981 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Goldblatt, Louis, 1946, 1973-1983 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Imada, Mary, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - ??? Ito, Ritsu, 1980-1981 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Jackson, Jesse, 1985, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - ???? Kato, Kanju, 1935, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      Also includes a group photograph of the Kanju Kato Reception Committee taken on July 27, 1935 and reception announcements.
    - ???? Kamijo, Tsunehiko, 1973-1987 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - ???? Kaneko, Kiichi and Josephine Conger, 1977-1983 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Koide, Joe (= ???? Ukai, Nobumichi), 1953-1977 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      Also includes correspondence from James Oda and Paul Shinsei Kochi.
    - ???? Miyagi, Yotoku, 1962-1965, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence from Seiichi Nishitsuji, ???? Sakai Tsuneji (= Nishiuji Tsunejiro), and Paul Shinsei Kochi, and Yotokus illustration for a cover of "Puroretaria Geijutsu" no. 3 (May, 1931).
    - ???? Nosaka, Sanzo, 1961-1992 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Oda, James (1 of 2), 1978, 1992-1995 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      Also includes Yoneda's letters to Yuji Ichioka.
    - Oda, James (2 of 2), 1970-1978 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Onizuka, Kamezo, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Includes materials about Onizuka Kamezo, a Hawaii sugar plantation worker.
    - Reynolds, Malvia, 1970, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Shirai, Jack, 1960-1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ????? Takeuchi, Tetsugoro, 1971-1972, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      Also includes correspondence from H. Kawakami.
    - ???? Tsukahara, Taro, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Robert F., 1971 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - ????? Yokoi, Kumiko, 1979-1988 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Early Japanese Socialists in the United States, 1971-1979 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      Kaneko, Kiichi; ???? Tanaka, Chushichi; Yamaguchi, Kumao; Baba, Tatsui; Tachibana, Soichi; ??? Akaba, Hajime; Takano, Fusataro; ??? Nakahama, Tetsu; and others.
    - Japanese American Leftists, 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      Japanese American leftists under Japan's surveillance. Also includes lists of "1934-1941 U.S. Japanese Communists" with Yoneda's comments.
    - Japanese American Activists: ????????? Zaibei Nihonjin Mumei Senshi = Japanese American Unknown Soldiers, 1963-1969 (Box 39, Folder 10)
      "?????????? Zaibei Nihonjin Gassosha Meibo" compiled by Yoneda, and materials by ???????????? Kaiho Undo Giseisha Gasso Tsuitokai and ??????????? Kaiho Undo Mumei Senshi Tsuitokai, and correspondence from Hotta Kiyoshi.
    - Japanese Americans: Issei and Kibei, 1952-1993 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Japanese Americans: Nisei, 1975-1993 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Japanese American Individuals in Politics, 1964-1985 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      Also includes other Asian Americans.
    - Individual Activists, 1945, 1970-1992 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      Erickson, Oscar A.; Fee, Benjamin; Gold, Sam; Hermosa, Mario; King, Martin Luther, Jr.; Kroll, Leo; Mercado, Victoria; Olsen, Tillie; Rapport, Morris; Schmidt, Henry; Stalinger, Preston; Taylor, John C.; Winston, Henry; and others. Also includes Yoneda's tributes to some of the activists.
    - Women Activists, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      News clippings on individual women activists published from 1942 to 1945.
    - ??? Ito, Ritsu, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 10.2 Political Activities and Subjects, 1905-1995, bulk 1962-1995
    Comprised mainly of collected publications, including news clippings, fliers, brochures, and newsletters regarding political activities and subjects. Some files include Yoneda's notes and correspondence. In English and Japanese. All folders are listed in alphabetical order.
    - Angel Island Detention Center, 1974-1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Anti-Marcos Campaign, 1971-1982 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Asian American Federation of Union Members, 1982-1987 (Box 40, Folder 7)
      Also includes the transcripts of Yoneda's speech, "A Benefit for Asian/Pacific American Federation of Union Members" delivered on November 18, 1983, and meeting minutes, bylaws, etc.
    - Asian and Asian American Community: Asian Immigrants, Workers, and Strikes, 1973-1987 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Asian and Asian American Community: Asian Population in the U.S., 1982-1991 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Asian and Asian American Community: Filipinos in the U.S., 1970-1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Asian American Newspapers, 1969-1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      The Activist; Ang Katipunan; Asian Law Caucus; Bay Area Asian Coalition against the War Newsletter; Getting Together; Gidra; In Struggle; Kalayaan; Korea Bulletin; Korea Focus; Philippine Liberation Courier; Puerto Rico Libre; Red Guard; The Worker; U.S. Vietnam Friendship Association Newsletter; and Yellow Pearl.
    - Asian American Publications, 1969-1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      Also contains lists of books on Asian Americans available in the United States compiled by the Japanese American Curriculum Project, Inc. (JACP, Inc.) and "A Chronological History of the Japanese Newspapers in America 1880s-1941" compiled by Seizo Oka.
    - Asian Pacific American Advocates of California (APAAC) and Asian Pacific American Coalition USA (APAC), 1983-1990 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      Seven issues of: APAAC Alert. Sacramento: APAAC; six issues of: APAC Alert. San Francisco: Asian Pacific American Coalition U.S.A. Also includes meeting minutes, correspondence, and news clippings.
    - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA), 1982-1992 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      Also Includes the transcripts of Yoneda's speech delivered at the APALA founding convention in 1992.
    - Association for Asian American Studies: Special Board of Directors' Pioneer Award, 1991-1992 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Yoneda's reception of the special Board of Directors' Pioneer Award from the Association for Asian American Studies.
    - Bay Area Labor History Workshops, 1982-1995 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      Includes meeting minutes and conference materials.
    - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors, 1962-1967 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Committees of Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Free Angela Davis Campaign, 1971-1984 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Hawaii Alliance, 1980-1989 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      Fourteen issues of: News of the Hawaii Alliance. Honolulu: Hawaii Alliance, 1980 -1989. Also includes conference brochures sponsored by the Hawaii Alliance.
    - Hawaii Pono Journal, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 1)